<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Curriculum Vitae - Ian Stahnke</title>
    <link>https://pr8kerl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Curriculum Vitae - Ian Stahnke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 23:38:42 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pr8kerl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>technical</title>
      <link>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/technical/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 23:38:42 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/technical/</guid>
      <description> Recent Technical Skills  AWS – well versed in Cloudformation, EC2, VPC, S3, Route53, ECS, Kinesis, Direct Connect, CloudFront, Lambda, API Gateway Containerized application deployment using Kubernetes and ECS DevOps toolsets such as git, docker, docker-compose, Buildkite, Jenkins, Ansible, Puppet General purpose programming in Golang, Bash, Perl, Python and Ruby Web programming in Golang, Javascript, Node.js. Content Management System implementation and administration - Adobe Experience Manager 6.X, Fatwire, Wordpress In-depth experience in web technologies such as Apache Web Server, Squid, Haproxy, Tomcat, JBOSS, AEM, Fatwire Security Management, Vulnerability management, PCI compliance, Openvas, Qualys, PKI management, OpenSSL, PGP Systems Monitoring: Nagios, Prometheus, Graphite, Influxdb Splunk (large distributed deployment) Experience of IP networks, Load balancing (F5), Firewalls (Palo) Experience working in an Agile environment ITIL v3 certified  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>employment</title>
      <link>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/employment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 23:38:42 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/employment/</guid>
      <description>MYOB Australia, Melbourne Senior Devops Engineer Jan 2017 – Present Duties As part of the centralised Devops Platform Enablement team, provide common tools and patterns for deployment of applications and cloud infrastructure. Develop and maintain software solutions that solve common problems for development teams. Support and develop centralised logging solution based on AWS Kinesis, Lambda and Splunk. Support and develop infrastructure and application monitoring using Prometheus, Datadog and NewRelic. Maintain and support managed infrastructure based on Kubernetes in AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>education</title>
      <link>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 23:38:42 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pr8kerl.github.io/cvsections/education/</guid>
      <description>Professional Training  2015 Advanced Architecting on AWS - Bespoke Training Services, Melbourne 2015 Adobe Experience Manager Sites: System Administration - Adobe Training Services, Melbourne 2013 ITIL Foundation Certificate v3 2012 Architecting on AWS - AWS Education, Melbourne 2011 Alienvault USM for Security Engineers - Alienvault, Melbourne 2008 RedHat Certified Engineer - Liga LinDist ApS, Copenhagen 2007 Oracle 10G Administration Workshop I – Bonner, Frankfurt 2006 SAP Administration and Authorisation - EUMETSAT, Darmstadt 2005 HP Openview Operations for UNIX I – HP UK, London 2004 Solaris Performance Analysis – Sun Education, Melbourne 2003 Sun Cluster 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>